Welcome back to the Engine Room Records
Planetarium!
Having crossed the Roche limit, the structural
integrity of our satellite has officially
failed.
We are now experiencing terminal
fragmentation as tidal forces overcome
gravitational self-attraction.
The celestial body shatters into a
high-velocity debris field!
Please remain seated. Embrace.
For immediate impact.
The ground is cracking right beneath my boots.
We're ripping up the foundation, pulling the
roots. The sky is falling in a million jagged
pieces. The pressure building up and it never
releases.
I look up and the moon is ripped in half. Nothing
left to do but watch it burn and laugh.
The gravity is dead, the center cannot hold The
chorus spilling out a story never told It's
raining heavy metal from a shattered sky Kiss
the quiet sanctuary a bitter goodbye
Fragmentation, we're blowing it apart A
million flying pieces of a heavy metal heart
FRAGMENTATION! WELCOME TO THE CRASH! TURNING
ALL THE HISTORY TO CINDERS AND TO ASH! WE'RE
LIVING IN THE MIDDLE OF A DEBRIS FIELD! NO
BLASTERS! NO SHELTER! NO SHIELD!
FRAGMENTATION!
I CAN SEE THE BLACK GUITARS FALLING THROUGH THE
SPACE! A violent collision in the human race The
magma is spilling from the broken crust Turning
all the monuments to powder and dust You wanted a
reaction, you wanted a spark Well now we're
throwing fire right into the dark
The gravity is dead, the center cannot hold The
chorus spilling out a story never told It's
raining heavy metal from a shattered sky Kiss
the quiet sanctuary a bitter goodbye
Fragmentation, we're blowing it apart A
million flying pieces of a heavy metal heart
FRAGMENTATION! WELCOME TO THE CRASH! TURNING
ALL THE HISTORY TO CINDERS AND TO ASH! WE'RE
LIVING IN THE MIDDLE OF A DEBRIS FIELD! NO BLAST
DOORS! NO SHELTER! NO SHIELD! FRAGMENTATION!
Thank you.
FRAGMENTATION! WE'RE BLOWING IT APART! A
MILLION FLYING PIECES OF A HEAVY METAL HEART!
FRAGMENTATION! WELCOME TO THE CRASH! TURNING
ALL THE HISTORY TO CINDERS AND TO ASH! WE'RE
LIVING IN THE MIDDLE OF A DEBRIS FIELD! NO BLAST
DOORS! NO SHELTER! NO SHIELD! FRAGMENTATION!
NO SHIELDS IN THE DEBRIS FIELDS! WATCH IT
SHATTER!